[
    {
        "front": "Tonari ",
        "back": "Next to",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kagi ",
        "back": "Keys",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Watashitachi",
        "back": "We, us",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Anata",
        "back": "You (informal)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaishain",
        "back": "Company Employee",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Shain",
        "back": "Company Employee",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Ginkōin",
        "back": "Bank Employee",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Isha",
        "back": "Doctor",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Daigaku",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Byōin",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Biyōin",
        "back": "Beauty Parlor",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kun",
        "back": "Equivalent to san (Used for younger ones)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Denki",
        "back": "Electricity",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Denkiyasan",
        "back": "Electronic showroom",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Onamae",
        "back": "(Your) Name",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Heya",
        "back": "Room",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Tabako",
        "back": "Ciggarette",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Suimas",
        "back": "To smoke, to inhale",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Chigaimas",
        "back": "To differ, its different",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Bijutsukan",
        "back": "Art museum",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yūbinkyoku",
        "back": "Post Office",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Sūpā",
        "back": "Supermarket",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Torimas",
        "back": "To take, To pass",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Aimas",
        "back": "To meet",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Mise",
        "back": "Shop",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Shukudai",
        "back": "Homework",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Daitai",
        "back": "Almost",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yoku",
        "back": "Often",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Sukoshi",
        "back": "Little",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Zenzen",
        "back": "Not at all",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Seikatsu",
        "back": "Lifestyle, Daily life",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Donna",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yakyū",
        "back": "Baseball game",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Uta",
        "back": "Song",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Utaimas",
        "back": "To sing",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "E ",
        "back": "Painting",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yakusoku",
        "back": "Promise",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Hayaku",
        "back": "Quickly",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Osoku",
        "back": "Late",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kodomo",
        "back": "Child, Children",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Hako",
        "back": "Box",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Shashin",
        "back": "Photograph",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Mono",
        "back": "Things",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Sonohoka",
        "back": "Besides, Other than this",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "~Ya ~Ya ~Nado",
        "back": "~, ~, ~etc.",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Taihen",
        "back": "Hard, tiresome",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "ōi",
        "back": "Large number",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Iroiro",
        "back": "Various\n<na-adj.>",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yori",
        "back": "Compared to",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "zutto",
        "back": "By far (While comparing)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kūkō",
        "back": "Airport",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Kondo",
        "back": "Next",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Dare / Donata",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Nansai / Oikutsu",
        "back": "How Old",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Nan / Nani",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Doko / Dochira",
        "back": "Where",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikura",
        "back": "How much (Money)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Itsu",
        "back": "When",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Dō / Dōyatte",
        "back": "How",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Donna",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōshite",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Dore / Dono",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikutsu",
        "back": "How many",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Donokurai",
        "back": "How long",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Dochira",
        "back": "Which (option)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Naze",
        "back": "Why (polite)",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Umi",
        "back": "Sea, Ocean",
        "chapter": 11
    },
    {
        "front": "Yama",
        "back": "Mountain",
        "chapter": 11
    }
]